拜托 为什么它们都不跟着我
Come on. Why aren't they transferring to me?
我跟你一模一样啊
I look just like you.
可能我的气味不对
Maybe I don't have the scent right.
几周前 我发现了一窝鸭蛋
A few weeks ago, I found a nest of duck eggs.
我 我悉心照料
I, uh... I lovingly nursed them,
结果 某些人撞狗屎运
and then, uh, by some...sick fluke,
鸭子出生时 只有克莱尔在场
Claire was the only one there when the ducks were born,
所以它们把她印刻于心了
so they imprinted on her.
我不是故意的啊
Oh, I didn't do it on purpose.
那就让它们回到我身边啊
Then make them come back to me.
谁这个点儿打电话啊
Who's calling at this hour?
你好
Hello?
怎么了
Yes?
卢克被捕了
Luke's been arrested!
早上好 莱纳德
Well, good morning, Leonard.
莱纳
Leonar--
我知道我的乖儿子卢克
I know it's not my well-behaved son, Luke,
才不会没拿驾照就偷开我们的车出去
who'd never take our car out without a license
然后被捕
and get arrested.
我偷开车出去是有正当理由的
I took the car for a good reason.
萨拉·费舍尔的猫死了 她悲痛至极
Sarah Fisher's cat died, and she was devastated,
所以我猜她可能会想要跟我亲热
so I thought she might make out with me.
结果在离她家两个街区的地方被抓了
I got caught two blocks away from her house.
所有人泡妞的运气都超好 除了我
Everyone is having great luck with girls except for me.
我真的是指所有人
And I mean everyone.
皮疹什么时候不是皮疹呢
When is a tuba-strap rash not a tuba-strap rash?
当它是吻痕的时候
When it's hickeys.
我们得限制你外出
You know, we're gonna have to ground you,
不止这些哦
Oh, we're doing way more than that.
兰登要赚回300块钱的罚款
Landon has a $300 fine to work off.
这点我们可以争辩一下 就说条子有种族歧视
We could fight that -- say the cop was racist.
即便我们输了 也会引发一场讨论
Even if we lose, it'll start a conversation.
你犯了错误 就得付出代价 莱翁
You made a mistake, you pay the consequences, Levon.
你的第一份工作就是清理
Your first job is cleaning out
我为我的鸭子们建的完美小村庄
the awesome village I built for my ducks.
不是老妈的鸭子吗
Aren't they mom's ducks?
你真想现在来挑战我的极限吗
Do you really want to test me right now?!
你 先生 慢慢做决定吧
Well, you, sir, take your time deciding.
我们会像猎犬在木橱柜的阴影里
We'll be here just as sure as a coonhound
夏日小憩一样待在这里一动不动
takes a summer nap in the shade of a Chifferobe.
好了 你现在只是在随便背
Okay, now you're just randomly throwing words together
《杀死一只知更鸟》里的台词罢了
from "To Kill a Mockingbird."
今年农场的番茄获得了大丰收
It was a boon year for tomatoes on the farm,
或者是我们所说的
or what we're calling...
番大富
Tomatogeddon.
所以他们做了超大一批的"塔克超有名"
So they made an extra-large batch of Tucker's Famous,
我们要在农夫市集上卖掉
and we're selling it at the farmers' market.
你说的"有名"
Now, when you say "Famous" --
指的是全密苏里州境内有名
it's known Missouri-wide.
一个死刑犯点名要在他的最后一餐上吃这个
A death-row inmate requested it for his last meal.
至少我在努力卖啊
Well, at least I'm trying to sell.
怎么了
What is going on?
在买了那边卖的东西之后
After buying whatever they're selling,
我猜人们没钱再买东西了吧
I'm guessing people are plum out of spending money.
等等 不
Wait. No.
是安德鲁和西蒙
It's Andrew and Simon.
谢谢
Thank you.
-你好呀 -你好
- Hello. - Oh, hello!
要试试我们手抓手作的鳟鱼干吗
Here to try our hand-caught artisanal trout jerky?
-不用了 -卖得跟烤饼一样好
- No. - It's selling like hotcakes.
其实是更好
Actually, better.
看到素食烤饼摊了吗
See the vegan hotcakes stand?
就在订做蜂蜜摊旁边
Next to the bespoke honey stall.
我们该小心点 这个市集可能是个陷阱
We should be careful. This market might be a trick
把一堆白人都聚集到一个地方
to get a whole bunch of white people together in one spot.
我其实很高兴你有来
I'm actually glad you're here.
我们在找新的高级项目经理
We're looking for a new senior associate,
我正打算找你
and I was gonna call you.
找我干什么 一个过气的人
Call me what? A has-been?
"米事生非"吗
"Mitch ado about nothing"?
我为什么要为你干你的活
Why am I doing your work for you?
听着 从社交上 我觉得你真的不可救药了
Look, on a social level, I find you hopeless,
但我总觉得你是个好律师
But I always thought you were a good lawyer --
如果到了对的律所 说不定就是个很厉害的律师了
Maybe a great one at the right firm.
亲爱的 你有带别的现金盒吗
Honey, did you bring the other cash box?
这个装满了
This one's filled up.
考虑一下吧
Think about it.
拜托 乔
Come on, Joe!
我不想学
I don't want to learn!
但你必须学
But you have to learn!
非常简单
And it's so easy.
听着 首先你要先做个小人
Look, first, you make the little man,
然后你用绳子缠住他的喉咙
then you tie the rope around its throat --
不要
No!
乔 别担心系鞋带的事情
Joe, don't worry about tying your shoes.
那是大男孩才做的
That's for big boys.
别告诉他不行
Don't tell him he can't.
他不行 但那不会怎么样
He can't, but he'll be fine --
我们孩子有浓密美丽的头发
kid has thick, beautiful hair.
-我可以继续工作了吗 -你在工作吗
- Can I get back to work now? - You're working?
但现在又不是周一到周四的
But it's not between 10:00 and 2:00,
10点到下午2点
Monday through Thursday.
我本不打算告诉你们
Well, I wasn't gonna tell you guys,
因为我知道你们又会小题大做
'cause I knew you'd make a big fuss,
但商会要授予我
but the chamber of commerce is giving me
工业巨人奖
a titans of industry award.
他们请我们为庆典录个有关
They asked me to make a video for the ceremony
我奋斗动力的视频
about what drives me.
在经过了30年
After 30 years
安装了成百上千万的吊衣杆后
and over a hundred thousand hanger rods installed,
有些人会就此安定 放松一下
some people would kick back and relax.
但我不会 我可是杰·普里契特
Not me. I'm Jay Pritchett.
普里契特橱柜
Pritchett's closets.
慢点慢点
Slow down!
你需要多少橱柜
How many closets do you need?
好的 我能搞定
Yeah. I can handle that.
-好棒 -我要重新录
- It's great. - I'm starting over.
-为什么 -你们觉得很无聊
- Why? - You guys were bored,
这段视频明显没有体现我的精髓
and the video obviously doesn't capture my essence.
你们觉得另一个巨人 漆布之王艾德·菲斯克
You think that fellow titan Ed Fisk, the lion of linoleum,
也会犯这种错误吗
would make that mistake?
这次活动有多盛大啊
How big is this event?
会有红毯吗
Is there going to be a red carpet?
没有 但是莱德[红]地毯的莱德·莫塔会去
No, but Red Murtaugh, of Red's carpets, will be there.
我可是要跟一帮行业巨人并肩前行 歌洛莉亚
I'm walking with giants, Gloria,
很容易因此被别人超越[踩到]
and that's a good way to get stepped on.
那里有两个位置
Oh, there are two over there.
太好了 我还以为我们永远找不到了
Oh, good. For a second, I didn't think we were gonna find...
那不是贝丝和安迪吗
Hey, isn't that Beth and Andy?
其实那两个位置更好一点
Um, actually, uh, those two are better.
但那样我们会离得好远啊
But all those people would be between us.
是啊 但是我们已经在一起一天了
Yeah, but, you know, we spent all day together.
-我 -你们好呀
- I just -- - Hey. Hey, you two.
安迪 你瘦下来了好棒啊
He y, Andy. Very cool you're not fat anymore.
你们好 很高兴见到你们
Hi! Nice to see you guys!
我们应该趁电影还没开始去找座位...
We really should go find seats before the m--
请坐下
Sit down, please.
安迪订婚后
Ever since Andy got engaged,
我们之间就怪怪的
things between us have been weird.
就好像"一个想扯掉自己红头发的
Like "a woman with olive skin
橄榄色肤色女人"那样诡异
trying to pull off red hair" weird.
我只想赶紧看完电影
I just wanted to watch the movie
在情况变尴尬前离开那里
and get out of there before it got awkward.
我还在想念你
I still think about you.
我也是 但我现在跟别人在一起了
Me too. But I'm with someone else now.
我已经许下承诺了呃
I made a commitment.
但你真的爱她吗
But do you really love her?
僵尸
Zombie!
干掉了
Got it!
我们早就应该告诉对方我们的真实想法
Anyway, we should have told each other how we felt.
没感觉吗 真的吗
Nothing? Really?
我恨不得越早离开越好
I could not get out of there fast enough.
急什么啊
What's the rush?
他们有时候会在演员名单后面弄个彩蛋
Sometimes they put a funny skit thing after all the names.
你们俩等一下
Guys, wait up.
你们想一起去隔壁吃个汉堡喝点啤酒吗
You want to go grab a burger and a beer next door?
我当然想了
Well, I -- I definitely do.
那部电影让我想到了太多
That movie brought up so much for me.
另外 我的药不能空腹吃
Plus, I got to take my pill with food.
-我不一定 -你要来哦
- Yeah, I'm not so sure -- - You're coming.
说不定你来了
Maybe if you're there,
他就不会为老板娘表演他可爱的
he won't try and do his adorable British character
英国调调
for the hostess.
你能把这个放到我的素汉堡里吗
Will you put this in my veggie burger
别告诉我放在哪里了
and not tell me where it is?
罗伊德 我是你爸 也是你最大的噩梦
Hey, Lloyd, it's your dad, A.K.A. your worst nightmare.
只是想提醒你一下你得把鸭村
Just reminding you the duck village
洗到能在里面盛食物吃的程度
needs to be clean enough to eat off of.
听到了吗 最好没听到
You hear me? You better not have.
因为你不被允许使用电话
You're not allowed to use your phone.
没错 我无处不在
Yep, I'm everywhere.
你对卢克是不是有点太严厉了
You think maybe you're being a bit hard on Luke?
我们是他父母 克莱尔
We're his parents, Claire.
防止他走向歧途是我们的责任
It's our job to keep him off the stripper pole.
其实我挺喜欢他有点小叛逆的
I actually like that he's being a little bit rebellious.
偶尔 除了玩魔术和蹦床之外
Sometimes, between the magic and the trampolining,
我觉得他有点 你懂的
I think he's getting a little... you know.
你想说什么 克莱尔
What are you trying to say, Claire?
有点 像我吗
A little...me?
又来了
There it was again,
她在影射我不够坏
the insinuation that I'm not dangerous enough for her.
很明显 她忘了我曾经进过监狱
Apparently, she's forgotten I've been to jail.
我曾经在翻跟斗疗法课堂上带过二十名犯人
I once led 20 violent inmates in a therapeutic tumbling class.
获得了巨大成功
It was a huge success.
我当时能把参与奖杯做得
Could I have made the participation trophies
不那么锋利吗
a little less stabby?
当然
Sure.
不过总之 巨大的成功
But overall, a huge success.
你说你喜欢卢克的叛逆...
When you say you're happy about Luke being a rebel...
你喷了我的香水吗
Are you wearing my perfume?
是为了吸引鸭子们
It was to trick the ducks.
像我刚才说的...
But like I was saying --
那是艾丽克斯吗
Hey, is that Alex?
是啊 真奇怪
It is. That's weird.
她说整个周末都要待在学校学习
She said she was gonna be at school all weekend studying.
喂
Hello?
亲爱的
Hey, honey.
我也在 你怎么样啊 亲爱的
I'm here, too. How are you doing, honey?
我很好 在干活呢 真是超级忙
Oh, yeah, I'm good. I'm doing some work. Really busy.
真有意思 因为...
Well, that's interesting, be--
是啊 我们今天也很无聊
Yeah, we've got a boring day ahead of us, too.
现在要去扣押车辆停车场取车
Heading down to the impound lot to pick up the car
因为没错 你弟昨晚被警察抓了
because, yes, your brother got arrested last night.
是吗 真好
Oh! Okay. Well, that's great.
我得挂了 我东西还放在图书馆呢
Yeah, I really got to go. I left my stuff in the library.
我超担心有人会偷我的零食
And I'm really worried someone's gonna steal my snacks.
就这样 挂了
Okay, bye!
你干嘛拦我 我差点就能抓她现行了
Why did you stop me? I was gonna bust her.
怎么 一个小谎言而已 拜托
What? In a little lie? I mean, come on.
她可能是去朋友家
She's probably visiting a friend
只不过不想让我们难过而已
and she didn't want to hurt our feelings.
她听到卢克被拘留几乎毫无反应
She barely reacted when she heard that Lluke got arrested.
她肯定有什么秘密
She's obviously hiding something.
她现在居然进卖酒的地方了
And now she's walking into that liquor store.
天哪 这样就严重了
Oh, no. Oh, no. Now, this is serious.
一个大学生去朋友家玩
A college student is visiting a friend,
他们还买了啤酒
and they're buying beer!
放松 菲尔
Relax, Phil.
这女孩都有两个专利了
This girl has two patents.
可她需要的是两位父母
What she needs is two parents.
好吧 我想说少管艾丽克斯一点也没什么
Okay, my point is, it wouldn't hurt Alex to loosen up.
我担心她会变得有点...
I mean, I'm worried that she's getting a little...
又来了
There it is again.
直说吧 克莱尔
Just say it, Claire --
你希望我们的孩子能野一点
You like our kids running wild
因为你担心他们变得
'cause you're worried they're too much
太像他们懦弱自卑的爸爸
like their namby-pamby dad,
老好人先生 平凡市市长
Mr. Goody-goody, Mayor of vanillatown.
是因为鸭子喜欢我更多你才不高兴吗
Is this 'cause the ducks like me better?
这是生物学现象 你知道的
That is biological, and you know it.
网上还有它们
There are videos of them online
跟着吸尘器到处跑的视频呢
following around a vacuum cleaner.
它们就是一群白痴
They're basically idiots!
天哪 等等 她要上那辆面包车
Oh, my god. Hang on. She's getting into that van.
-现在我们能担心了 -没错 我很担心
- Oh, now we're concerned! - Yes, I'm concerned!
那是辆破烂的修理面包车
That is a sketchy repair van
开车的很可能是她在网上遇到的那种
that is probably being driven by some middle-aged pervert
留着一根长指甲的中年变态
with one long fingernail that she met online.
天哪 快点 跟上他们
Oh, my god, go! Follow them!
多谢你把曼尼的画架借给我们
Thank you for lending us Manny's easel.
大家都喜欢那个酱吗
Did everyone love the sauce?
如果大家是指一千只蜜蜂
Well, if by "everyone" you mean a thousand bees
以及一匹逃出马圈的小马驹的话 是的
and a pony that escaped from the riding circle, yeah.
不是吧
Oh, no --
你是要录那种视频遗嘱
Is this video wills where you make us compete
好让我们在寻宝游戏里争抢你的遗产吗
in a scavenger hunt for your inheritance?
不 是为了我的泰坦奖 我告诉过你的
No. It's the video for my Titan award. I told you about it.
我在尝试展现力量和自信
I'm trying to project strength and confidence.
也许你该先把壁炉上
Maybe you should lose
写着"我恨周一"的加菲猫杯拿下来
the Garfield "I hate Mondays" mug on the mantel.
说得好
Good catch.
我等你说这句话等了一辈子
I've waited my whole life to hear you say those words.
-想来帮我一下吗 -当然
- Want to help me out here? - Yeah.
我需要转移一下注意力
I needed the distraction.
我这一整天都在纠结
I had spent enough of my day
西蒙的工作邀请
obsessing over Simon's job offer.
另外 我不知道
Plus, I don't know --
看到我强大的老爸
seeing my big, strong dad
用这么柔弱的姿态请我帮忙
reach out to me in a vulnerable way,
我有点 感动
it was -- it was kind of touching.
红色按键 你怎么可能看不到
The red button! How do you not see it?!
你没来之前我拿扫把都能开机
Before you got here, I was turning it on with a broom!
算了 吃午饭吧
Now just -- forget it. Let's get lunch.
-我只要... -跟我来
If I could just -- - Come with me!
好 把酱含在嘴里 轻轻搅动
Okay, hold the sauce in your mouth, swirl it around --
让它覆盖你的舌面 然后吞下去
really coat your tongue. Now swallow.
-不错吧 -好多了
- Right? - Much better.
杰 你吃这个酱的时候
Okay, Jay, what you're gonna want to do
最好先含在嘴里 再...
is hold the sauce in your mouth, sw--
我知道怎么吃
I know how eating works.
-还不赖嘛 -谢谢
- Not too shabby. - Thank you.
歌洛莉亚过世的姑姑也挺会做酱汁的
You know who else makes a mean sauce is Gloria's dead aunt.
那边就有
Oh, there it is right there.
你试试 我跟你说 好吃爆了
Try some. I'm telling you, it's life-changing.
我觉得我们不需要两种酱
I don't think we really need two sauces.
而且如果你的调味酱来自...
And sometimes, when you have sauces from --
你尝一下
Now you eat.
天哪 真的太好吃了
Oh, my god. That is amazing.
这个秘密配方
It's a secret recipe
在我们家族传了几代了
that has been in my family for generations.
你的家传酱在建国两百周年纪念日
Was your sauce buried in a local time capsule
被装进当地时间胶囊了吗 我的酱是哦
during the bicentennial? Because mine was.
我的伯祖母米兰达曾是唯一会做这个酱的人
My great-aunt Miranda was the only one that could make it,
而因为我是家族里没有嫁给秘鲁人的
and because I was the oldest girl
年龄最大的女儿
that didn't marry a Peruvian,
这个秘方被传给了我
the recipe passed down to me.
-把酱给我 -好吧
- Sauce me. - Right.
这个房子里没有多少东西
Ay, I don't have many things
跟哥伦比亚有关的东西
that remind me of Colombia here in the house,
不过现在有了
but now I do.
我们酱的配方超级秘密
Legend has it our sauce was so secret,
只被写在了一个地方
it was only written down one place.
我们从小到大每周日都吃这个
We grew up eating this every Sunday,
现在曼尼和乔也会吃了
and now Manny and Joe will, too.
它被反向纹在了一个跛脚的马僮身上
It was tattooed backwards on a lame stable boy.
你只能从镜子读出来
You could only read it in a mirror.
我能看一下你的配方吗
Mm, can I see that recipe?
我觉得你读出来会很失礼
Uh, uh, well, I think it's a little bit rude to read --
你撞到我的手了
Ay! You bumped my hand!
你毁了它 不是吧
You've ruined it! No!
不 我能把它弄干
No, no! I can dry it! I can dry it!
不 墨水都花了 小卡
No, now the ink's running. Cam!
不 你又把我伯祖父的餐巾给毁了
No, and now you have ruined my great-uncle's napkins!
这桌上的东西都有特殊含义吗
It's okay, does everything at this table have meaning?
抱歉我来晚了
Hey, sorry I'm late.
我的新欢瑞秋需要我帮忙
My new lady, Rachel, needed help
选一条短裤好气气她继父
picking a pair of shorts to make her stepdad mad.
我在想哪个更讽刺
I wonder what's more of a "Screw you" --
是你给我讲这个故事 还是这群蠢鸭子
you telling me that story or that the ducks now stare at me
一边往浴室走一边盯着我
while they slowly go to the bathroom?
你们家不是有三只鸭子的吗
Didn't you guys have three ducks?
是啊 一只 两只
Yeah -- one, two...
糟糕了
Oh, no.
不好
Dude!
糟了
No, no, no, no, no, no!
他去哪里了
Where did he go?
我们可以试试这个鸭叫软件
Hey, look, there's a duck-call app we can use.
可千万别吵到她
Oh, crap. Not her.
这位是什么情况
What happened with this one?
我跟她处了一阵
Well, I was seeing her for a while,
后来她把我回绝了
then she pulled her shade down.
真经典 准备好
Classy. Get ready.
快闪
Scatter!
你在干什么
What the hell are you doing?
你是在偷拍我穿比基尼睡觉的图片吗
Are you taking pictures of me sleeping in a bikini?
不 我只是想试着把这只可怜的小鸭子
No! I was just trying to lure that little duckling
引回我朋友家的院子
back into my friend's yard.
天哪
Oh, my God!
-它太可爱了 -谢谢
- It's so cute! - Thank you.
你还专门来找他 真是太贴心了
You're adorable for looking after him.
我觉得我好像在学校见过你
Hey, you know, I think I've seen you around school before.
-我叫塔米 -我是曼尼
- I'm Tammy. - Manny.
这都行啊
You have got to be kidding me.
是什么让杰·普里契特一路前行
What drives Jay Pritchett?
是永不重复自我的欲望
A desire never to repeat himself.
我要再来一遍
Let me do that again.
是什么让杰·普里契特一路前行 奥迪轿车
What drives Jay Pritchett? An Audi.
我要说个笑话来开场吗 我要模仿莱德·莫塔
I'm gonna start with a joke? I'm following Red Murtaugh.
他太搞笑了
The man's hilarious.
你看过他在那个广告里扮成小婴儿吧
You've seen him be that baby in his ads.
提醒你一下
Just so you know,
摄影机的电池只够用11个小时 所以
the camera only has 11 hours of battery, so...
来验收一下吧
Let's see what we've got.
好
Yep.
我为什么看起来这么苍白 还汗津津的
Why do I look so pale and sweaty?
因为你老了 还有爱尔兰血统
Oh, well, you're old and Irish.
歌洛莉亚 我只是想跟你说
Gloria, again, I just want to say that I'm--
想说你很抱歉 你说过了
You're sorry? You told me.
是啊 你要原谅我 那是个意外
Yes, and, uh -- excuse me -- that it was an accident.
真的是意外吗
Was it?
当然是意外
Yes, of course.
我觉得是意外 我也说不清
I think. I -- I don't know.
你毁掉了我的孩子接触他们过去的机会
you have destroyed my children's connection to their past,
然后你觉得自己可能是故意的
and you might have done it on purpose?
对不起
I'm sorry.
安德鲁在农夫集市上羞辱了我
Andrew humiliated me today at the farmers' market,
我一直为了酱的事情跟别人竞争
and I've always been sauce-competitive...
让我帮你重新把它做出来
Look, just let me help you re-create it.
我只在八岁的时候看我阿姨做过一次
I saw my aunt make it once when I was 8 years old.
你以为我会记得吗
You think I'm going to remember--
-芫荽 -什么
- Cilantro! - What?
刚才那辆车逆火的声音听起来像枪声
That car backfiring, it sounded like gunshots.
我记得我还是个小女孩时 坐在阿姨的厨房里
I remember when I was a little girl in my aunt's kitchen,
她用力地剁芫荽 发出很大的声音
and she started chopping the cilantro really loud
这样我们就听不见外面的声音
so that we couldn't hear the noise.
你还记得什么
Yes, okay. Well, what else do you remember?
记不得了 小卡 已经过了30年
Well, nothing, Cam. It was 30 years ago.
那份食谱就在你心里 你只是需要把它找出来
No, the recipe is inside you! It just needs to come out!
妈妈 我找到了
Mommy, I found it.
-柠檬汁 -什么
- Lemon juice! - What?
看吧 我说过了只是早晚的事
Oh, see? I told you it's just a matter of time!
刺山柑 墨西哥辣椒
Capers, Jalapeno,
还有一点点黑胡椒
and a dash of black pepper!
我觉得真是很悲哀
It's just so sad.
男主角决定跟一个他完全不爱的僵尸
The guy decides to spend the rest of his life
过完余下的一生
with some zombie he doesn't love.
你们的桌已经准备好了
Your table is ready.
太好了 一大筐薯条[模仿英国腔]
Smashing! A bucket of chips--
今天你就别给我闹了
We're not doing that.
好吧
Okay.
我就问你一句
Hey, um, real quick--
为什么跟我一起看刚才的电影
why wasn't it more uncomfortable
你一点反应也没有
for you to watch that movie?
因为僵尸杀了我爸妈
Right. Because zombies killed my parents.
随你了
Oh, never mind.
我都忘了你根本没法成熟起来
I forgot you can't have an adult conversation.
别走 听我说
No, okay, yes.
如果几个月前我们一起看那部电影
If -- if we would have watched that movie a few months ago,
我会觉得很尴尬 但是
it would have been really weird, but...
我们现在不是挺好的吗
we're all good now, right?
是啊 我们没问题了
Oh, yeah. No, I mean, I am good.
迪伦和我已经重归于好
Dylan and I picked up right where we left off.
我就是问问你怎么样
I was just checking on you.
因为有一阵你有点不对
Cause for a while there, you were getting a little, uh...
是啊
Yeah.
贝丝在我身边呢
Beth stood by me.
站的比谁都近
Well, you know, as close as she could.
所以我知道我选对人了
That's when I knew I was with the right person.
别误解我
And -- and don't get me wrong --
我还是喜欢你的
I was -- I was pretty hung up on you.
但当我脑海里只剩下最后一个人的时候
But once I got it down to only one woman in my head,
我看到贝丝完全不同的一面
I saw Beth in a whole new way,
因此我们的关系才能继续发展
and we were able to move forward.
我理解
That makes sense.
我为你高兴
I'm happy for you.
看看我们 落难兄妹[模仿英国腔]
Look at us, brother and sister,
自幼与父母分离[模仿英国腔]
separated from our mum...
你演的太好了
Oh, you're so good at that.
你有没有想过
Hey, what do you think about
邀请海莉和迪伦来参加婚礼
inviting Haley and Dylan to the wedding?
很好啊
I love that idea.
而且是你提出来的 真是太好了
And I love you for having it.
你说为什么现在的人不说"赶巧儿了"
Why do you think people stopped saying "Coinkydink"?
迪伦 我
Dylan, um...
天哪
Oh, God.
你又要跟我分手了对不对
You're breaking up with me again, aren't you?
抱歉 我
I'm sorry. I just -- I --
我觉得安迪和贝丝
I feel like Andy and Beth
还有所有人 大家的关系都在发展[前进]
and everyone in the world are moving forward,
只有我们反而倒退
and we're moving backward.
我们要停下来
Actually, we're stopping,
因为我要下车
because I want to get out of the car.
-迪伦 -停车
- Dylan-- - Stop!
我受够了这样被你耍着玩
I'm tired of being jerked around.
我也要前进了
Now I'm moving forward, too.
你好歹叫个优步吧
Can't you at least call an Uber?
因为我老是跟司机闲聊 已经上了黑名单了
You know they banned me for talking too much to the drivers!
她还是不接电话 我不敢相信我们居然跟丢了
She's still not answering. I can't believe we lost them.
我们就要到家了 我可以在电脑上定位她的手机
We're almost home. I can track her phone from the computer.
"我希望你能电脑定位成功
"I hope you can track her phone
因为你连辆面包车都跟不住"
better than you tracked that van."
抱歉 克莱尔 就因为我有1/64的彻罗基血统
I'm sorry, Claire. Just because I'm 1/64th Cherokee,
不代表我天生擅长追踪
it doesn't make me a natural tracker.
你发现我没在追究这事了吧
You realize I'm not participating in this.
是啊 你已经说得很清楚 因为我开车太娘
Well, you made it pretty clear it was my fault we lost them
所以我把他们跟丢了
due to my less-than-manly driving.
-我的天 -是啊 我又开始了
- Oh, my God. - Yes, this again.
除非你承认我是个男人 不然我不会停的
I'm not letting it go till you admit that you wish I was a --
菲尔 是那辆面包车
Phil, it's the van!
-在我们家门口 -不好
- In my own house?! - Oh, no!
-先别急 -别拦我 克莱尔
- Okay, now, hang on. - Don't hold me back, claire!
虽然我只有1/64彻罗基血统
I may be one 1/64th Cherokee,
但我的63/64是个愤怒的白人老爸
but I'm also 63/64ths crazy white guy!
他人呢
Where is he?!
-你还好吗 -你在说什么啊
- Are you okay? - What are you talking about?
-你没事吧 -我没事啊
- Are you okay? -I-I-I'm fine.
-我很抱歉 -你是该抱歉了
- No, I'm sorry! I-I -- - You are now!
鲁本
Reuben?
天哪 我把鲁本杀了
Oh, my God! I killed Reuben!
宝贝
Oh, babe?
出什么事了 流血了诶
What's going on? That's blood.
我得辩解一下 我没想到有人能发现
In my defense, I didn't think anyone would ever find out.
坚持住 鲁本
Stay with me, Reuben!
好吧 原来开面包车去接你的是鲁本吗
Okay, so Reuben is the one who picked you up in the van?
是的 那是他爸的车 天哪
Yes, it was his dad's -- oh, my god!
你们在跟踪我吗
Have you been following me?
他缓过来了 他会没事的
He's coming to. He's gonna be fine.
不 不要
No! No!
别想把过错推到我们身上
Don't try and make this our fault.
去酒水商店的那个人是你
You are the one who went to the liquor store
你买了什么
and bought - what?
冰
Ice.
罗本今天玩魁地奇的时候小腿扯着了
Reuben sprained his hamstring today while playing Quidditch.
宝贝 别误会我的意思 可你跟鲁本
Honey, don't take this the wrong way, but Reuben?
-我们相爱了 -闭嘴吧
- We're in love. - Oh, shut up.
不 别停 继续说话
No, no, no, keep talking!
还记得我们来之前发生了什么吗
Remember what happened when you tripped and fell
你怎么被绊倒的
right before we got here?
你知道吗 在加州理工真的很累
You know what? Caltech is hard.
身边有那么多的天才 我又跟桑杰分手了
Between all the geniuses and breaking up with Sanjay,
我只想跟让我觉得舒服的人在一起
I just wanted something comfortable,
即使他是个崇拜我的小呆瓜跟屁虫
even if it is a wormy little dork that worships me.
宝贝 我能理解
Oh, honey, I understand.
真是有其母必有其女
Oh, like mother, like daughter, I guess.
好了 他会没事的
Okay. He's gonna be fine.
菲尔 过来跟我聊几句
Phil, come over here and talk to me for a second.
我想我们该做的事已经做完了
Well, I guess we're done with my thing already.
如果有那么一瞬间我让你觉得
If I was ever stupid enough to imply, for one second,
你对我来说还不够像个坏男生
that you were not bad boy enough for me,
现在我绝对没有那样认为
I couldn't possibly think that right now.
因为我袭击了一名十六岁的男孩吗
Because I attacked a 16-year-old?
你当时都不知道衣橱里的人是谁
You didn't know who was in that closet.
那是真的
That's true.
看啊 他起来了
Look, he's up.
好吧 我们俩让你们单独待会儿吧
Okay, we're gonna leave the two of you alone.
等等 不用
Oh, wait, wait, wait, no, no, no.
你们不会把这事告诉别人的 对吗
Yeah, we're not gonna tell anyone about this, right?
禁忌之恋 让我更兴奋了
Forbidden love. It's -- it's hotter that way.
我还有个魔杖呢
Also, I -- I had a-a-a wand.
我真恨我自己
I hate myself so much.
味道不错
It's good.
当然不错了 我相信 好吧
Of course it's good. It's -- I'm sure -- o...kay.
天哪 太美味了
Oh, my gosh. It's glorious.
比我的好吃太多了
So much better than mine.
-你的酱汁 -就是垃圾
- Well, your sauce is -- - Is garbage!
主要就是番茄酱
It's mostly ketchup.
歌洛莉亚 这就是我们该放到
Gloria, this is what we need to be selling
农贸市场里卖的东西
at the farmers' market.
我们能让来买的人把队伍
We would have them lined up clear down
排得比那个卖纯天然海狸奶的还长
past the cruelty-free beaver-milk stand.
我会击垮安德鲁的
I would crush Andrew.
我不能再回农贸市场去了
I cannot go back to the farmers' market.
那是2011年
The year was 2011.
我刚从哥伦比亚回来
I had just come back from Colombia
带着满满一箱家里自制的顺发剂
with a box full of our family's homemade hair relaxer,
哥伦比亚柔顺王
the Colombian comb-out.
周五 我卖了五十瓶 可周六...
Friday, I sold 50 bottles, but Saturday...
瓶子上写着在头发上停留三分钟
It says on the bottle to leave it in for three minutes!
不 上面写得是"停留三个数
No, it says, "Leave in for three.
一会儿你的头发就会出奇得柔顺"[断句歧义]
Minutes later, you will look fantastic."
一 二 三 就梳开了
One, two, three, comb it out.
我知道问题出在哪里了
Ay, I see how it can be confusing.
如果是真的 如很多人推论的那样
If it's true, as many people theorize,
巨石阵实际上是古代祭司的衣橱
that stonehenge was, in fact, a druid closet --
米奇尔
Mitchell.
是的 很好 我们拍好了
Oh, yeah. Oh, good. We -- we got it!
你怎么了
What's with you?
真抱歉
I'm sorry.
抱歉 工作上的事让我很心烦
I'm sorry. I got this whole work thing stressing me out.
今天你走运了
It's your lucky day.
有个工业巨头来做你的听众
You have an audience with a titan of industry
而且你不用到高档的餐厅请我吃饭
without having to buy the $15-a-plate dinner ticket.
怎么回事
What's the issue?
我接到一个很大的事务所
Well, I got this job offer
给我的工作机会 但...
at this really big firm, but, um...
我其实 一直在考虑
I've actually, uh, been thinking about
也许该开一间自己的事务所
maybe starting my own practice.
-你的直觉是什么 -我不知道
- What's your gut tell you? - I don't know.
我很想有自己的事务所 但那真的很可怕
I-I would like to have my own firm, but that's really scary.
而这个工作机会又很吸引人
But this other offer is very attractive,
但我必须给一个我讨厌的人工作
but I'd have to report to this guy who I hate,
也许就是稳定工作的代价
which, you know, might be worth it for the job security --
-接受那个机会 -真的吗
- Take the offer. - Really?
经营自己的事业需要
It takes a certain type of personality
具备某种个性
to run your own thing.
你得是个斗士才能做到
You have to be a fighter.
真有意思
Well, this is fun.
是你想要我最忠恳的建议
You wanted my honest opinion.
不行 小卡 我说了不行
No, Cam! I said no.
极地冰盖融化了 华盛顿大塞车
The polar ice caps are melting, gridlock in Washington --
美国人需要再过得舒服点 歌洛莉亚
America needs to feel good again, Gloria.
让他们尝尝你的酱汁
Let them taste your sauce.
怎么回事
What's happening now?
他想让我在农贸市场卖我做的酱汁
He wants me to sell my sauce at the farmers' market,
但我不感兴趣
but I am not interested.
-我同意歌洛莉亚 -非常感谢
- I agree with Gloria. - Thank you so much.
是啊 上次卖那个发膏都让你崩溃了
Yeah, you crashed and burned with the hair thing.
你还需要更多那样的羞辱吗
You need more of that humiliation?
我们又不知道会不会再发生那样的事
We don't know that that would happen.
逐渐消失的中产阶级 种族骚乱...
Disappearing middle-class, racial unrest...
现在不是挺好的嘛 歌洛莉亚 享受吧
You got a nice thing going here, Gloria. Enjoy it.
什么 你觉得我做不了吗
What? You don't think that I can do it?
是的 他觉得你干不了
No. No, he doesn't.
他认为这家里只有他一个商业巨头
He thinks that he's the only business titan in this family.
没人可以告诉我什么能做什么不能做
Nobody can tell me what I can or cannot do.
我要去卖酱汁了
I have some sauce to sell.
而我现在要去注册我的新事务所了
And I'm gonna go register my new firm right now.
我也要愤然离去了
And I'm gonna storm out, too,
尽管那二位所做的事都让我很开心
even though both of those things actually make me very happy.
你们想知道是什么在鞭策杰·普里契特吗
You want to know what drove Jay Pritchett?
有人告诉我 我不够优秀
People telling me I wasn't good enough.
如果有人告诉你
There's something about a person telling you
你不能做某些事
you can't do something.
血
Blood.
那恰好点燃了好胜的火苗...
It just lights the competitive fires...
驱使我们去冒险
drives us to take risks...
为我们开启了新的机会
opens us up to new opportunities...
莎拉
Oh, hey, Sarah.
对你猫的事我感到很遗憾
I'm sorry about your cat.
我听说你被捕了
I heard you got arrested.
我所做的一切 都是在证明反对者是错的
Everything I did, I did to prove the naysayers wrong.
那些曾经认为我不够优秀的人...
So, to everyone who didn't think I was good enough --
看哪 爸爸 我自己系了鞋带
Look, Daddy! I tied my shoes!
干得好 乔
Good job, Joe!
脸疼不疼
how do you like me now?
亲爱的 我跟你一样不想参加那个泰坦奖晚宴
Honey, I don't want to go this titans dinner any more than you do,
但我们要迟到了
but we're gonna be late.
菲尔
Phil.
菲尔 菲尔
Phil. Phil!
邓菲
Dunphy.
你在干什么
What is going on?
我想付卢克的拘留费
I'm trying to pay Luke's impound fee,
但这个自动电话系统
but this automated phone system
根本听不懂我在说什么
doesn't understand anything I'm saying.
邓-菲
Dun-phy.
"邓菲" 对
"Dun-fee." Yes.
不对
No! No!
不是比尔·邓菲
Not Bill Dunphy.
在我名字这个问题上纠结了二十分钟了
We went over my first name for 20 minutes!
菲尔
Phil!